CONTACT

YE LIN PHYO

yelinphyocu@gmail.com

09459997942

No.34, Mae Zi Gone Rd, Hlaing TWP, Yangon

Portfolio: https://lin-smg.github.io/yelinphyo.dev Linkln: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ye-lin-phyo

OBJECTIVE -

I am an experienced software developer in innovating software designs, testing and coding as well as debugging programs and troubleshooting. To gain more working experience and contribute as much as I can to the place I work for. I would like to utilize my qualities of being patient, kindhearted, value based, knowledgeable and motivated for the work I am doing. I am highly motivated to work and earn experience for my career.

LANGUAGE-

English 4 Skills(Intermediate level)

EDUCATION-

2014 - 2019

Computer University (Magway)

Computer Science

B.C.Sc

SKILLS.

- Android development (java, flutter)
- PHP Framework(CI), Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Javascript, Nodejs, Eggjs, Nestjs, Vuejs, Nuxtjs,
- o Flutter
- MySQL, SQLite, Postgres
- o Rest, Protobuf
- o Others:
 - o Github, Gitlab, Figma, Firebase
- o Personal Skills:
 - Good interpersonal skills with adaptability and flexibility
 - Ability to work independently with minimum supervision
 - Ability to interact, co-ordinate and get along with co-workers and public contacts
 - Able to work well as part of a team

AWARDS-

- Rank 7 of upper Myanmar in Samsung Tech Institute Myanmar 2017 (Staff Entrance Android Application)
- Rank 2 of upper Myanmar in Science & Technology Fair 2018 (CropTrade Android Application)
- First Runner Up in First ICT Project Show & Competition 2018
 (ADM Android Application)
- Winner in Second ICT Project Show & Competition 2019 (Secure4U Android Application)

EXPERIENCE-

1.5.2019 - 31.7.2019 Innowave CO., Ltd

Internship

16.10.2019-30.11.2019 Innowave CO., Ltd

Software Developer (Android & PHP)

1.12.2019 - Now The Ninth Art CO., Ltd

Software Engineer (Vuejs, Eggjs)

PROJECTS

Academic Projects -:

Staff Entrance (Android)

Samsung Tech Institute Myanmar 2017

Android application using java. Competitive application.

Responsibility:

- · Gathering requirements
- · Defining system flow
- Develop part of quiz test and calculating score and report score.

CropTrade (Android)

Science & Technology Fair 2018

Android application using java. Competitive application.

Responsibility:

- · Gather requirements
- Define system flow and Database design
- Develop API using PHP

o ADM (Android)

First ICT Project Show and Competition 2018 (Computer University

Magway) Member : 2

Android application using java. Competitive application.

Responsibility:

- Requirement analysis
- Define system flow and Database design
- Develop API using PHP

o LMS (Web)

Computer University Magway

Learning Management System using PHP.

Features: student registration, class schedule management, assignment and monthly test and etc.

Responsibility:

- Define system flow and Database design
- Develop part of class schedule management and monthly test.

Secure4U (Android)

Second ICT Project Show and Competition 2019 (Computer University Magway)

Android application using java. Winner in Competition. Responsibility:

- Gather requirements
- Develop part of sending SMS of current device location for help.

Professional Projects -:

IWAVE POS Waiter (Android)

Innowave Co.,Ltd

Restaurant Waiter android app using Java Responsibility:

- Requirement Analysis
- Help UI development
- Backend API development using PHP and integration with main POS and MySQL database

ALUMNI

Innowave Co.,Ltd (internship)

Android app for alumni group to keep information and communication Alumni CMS using PHP CI (Codelgniter)

- Responsibility:

 Requirement Analysis
 - UI/UX development for android app and CMS
 - Lead CMS development team and define system flow and DB design.

IWAVE POS

Innowave Co.,Ltd

POS using PHP CI (CodeIgniter)

Responsibility:

- Add new features
- Testing and troubleshooting
- Support integration with POS waiter android app
- Maintenance and software installation

99-Agent Web App & Mobile

The Ninth Art Co.,Ltd

Game agent web app using Vuejs, Element UI and Mobile app using Vuejs, Vant.

Responsibility:

- Update new version using Vuejs from old Angular version
- Develop UI for both web and mobile app
- Develop one code base for both web and mobile
- Integrate Backend API and add new features (money recharge and withdrawal management) and maintenance

o 99-CMS Web App

The Ninth Art Co.,Ltd

Game admin web app using Vuejs, Element UI. Responsibility:

- Add new features in old CMS using Angular
- Develop new version using Vuejs
- Develop UI/UX using Element UI framework
- Integrate with backend server and maintenance

 Modify old function and add multi languages and new features (money recharge and withdrawal management)

Baijia Game

The Ninth Art Co., Ltd

Desktop game using Vuejs and Electron Responsibility:

- Develop Game UI for 1920x1080 resolution
- Develop accurate game result and complex game functions

Sangong Game

The Ninth Art Co., Ltd.

Desktop game using Vuejs and Electron Responsibility:

- Develop Game UI for 1920x1080 resolution
- Develop accurate game result and complex game functions

o Zxniuniu Game

The Ninth Art Co., Ltd

Desktop game using Vuejs and Electron Responsibility:

- Modify and analysis game UI
- · Add new feature and complex game functions

o 99-VIP-Contact (Web App & Server)

The Ninth Art Co., Ltd

Cars and rooms rental web app using Vuejs, Element UI and Backend server using Nodejs, Eggjs Responsibility:

- Frontend UI/UX development
- Develop part of deleting or recovering data in backend server
- Test and debug in backend server and report bugs to Chinese backend developer.

99-task (game points buy and sell app) (Mobile App & CMS & Backend Server)

The Ninth Art Co.,Ltd

Game coin selling and buying mobile app using Vuejs, Quasar framework and admin CMS using Vuejs, Element UI framework and backend server using Nodejs, Eggjs.

Responsibility:

- Mobile and CMS UI development
- Test and debug in mobile app, CMS and backend server.
- Report bugs to Chinese backend developer and repair bugs and report again.

Other Projects -:

Flutter

I am very interested in mobile development. I learn flutter in my free time and develop personal android application using flutter. So, I am sure I can contribute in professional flutter application development.

My personal projects :-

Task Planner

Android App (Flutter)

This is a task planner android application using Flutter. User can schedule tasks in advance and you will be notified when the time for the task is approaching.

Technology:

• sqflite, getx, get_storage

Crypto

Android App (Flutter)

This app is cryptocurrency application developed by using flutter. In this app, you can see information about crypto coins and cryptocurrency price and exchanges. The data will be updated every second. You can see latest cryptocurrency price and information.

Technology:

- getx, get_storage
- API: https://www.coingecko.com

Tractor Rental Service

Android App (Flutter)

This application was developed for farmer. User can record rental history and remember to get rental fee. This application supports multi languages (Eng,Mya). In this app, I'm using firestore for data storage and it make to sync data between users such as owner, driver and who collect rental fee.

Technology:

getx, get storage, firebase

https://lin-smg.github.io/yelinphyo.dev/projects(Download available)

STRENGTH-

- Critical thinker
- o Able to work a team, as well as independently
- Flexible and can easily adapt to learn new technology at any situation
- o Talented, self-motivated, active, energetic and enthusiastic
- Able to work under pressure
- Leadership and problem solving